No, no, no, you had your chance to be "we"
for like a year and a half now.
(Leonard:)Right now, you are you,
and you are screwed.
- Why do we have to tell him I did it?
- Not gonna tell him I did it.
(Penny:)Okay, okay, how about this?
(Penny:)We tell him somebody broke in.
(Leonard:)Just to shoot the couch
with a paintball gun?
(Penny:)I'm sorry, I buy it.
All those people are on drugs.
(Leonard:)We could tell him they wanted the couch
to stay away from their boyfriend.
(Penny:)Okay, fine.
Well, what if we just flip it over?
(Penny:)There. Looks fine, right?
(Leonard:)Butt print.
There's no discernible butt print.
(Penny:)Oh, come on.
(Penny:)There. Butt print.
(Leonard:)It's too small and too perfect.
(Penny:)- Thank you.
- You're welcome.